( COINS JANGLE )
How is everything , Mr. Sabian ?
- Great , as always . - Good .
You get home now , Eva . It 's getting late .
Stay safe .
Yeah . You , too , Mr. Sabian .
MAN : ( ON TV ) Traffic is building rapidly downtown ,
as citizens rush to get home before commencement .
If you 're not Purging , we advise you
to get off the streets as quickly as possible .
It 'll soon be a war out there .
Prognosticators estimate that more people
will partake in this year 's Purge ...
Sabian 's gone . That 's it .
What is she waiting for ? Why doesn 't this bitch let us go ?
Hey , calm down . We got plenty of time .
You girls up to anything fun tonight ?
I might kidnap Eva this year .
Hope that 's okay with you , mami .
MRS. CRAWLEY : It 's getting late .
Hope to see you all tomorrow . Stay safe .
Okay , stay safe .
CARLOS : Finally . Stay safe , Mrs. Crawley .
Eva .
Need a ride home ?
I 'm fine , Carlos .
Stay safe .
Bye , Carlito . Stay safe .
( INHALES SHARPLY )
If he asked to take me home , I 'd accept that ride , girl .
He 's a dog .
Oh , I like that dog . I would walk the shit out of that dog .
But that dog doesn 't want anything to do with me ,
he wants to sniff your ass .
- ( CHUCKLES ) You 're disgusting . - It 's true .
You 're really gonna ask her tonight ?
I have to .
I can 't afford his medicine much longer .
All right , good luck . ( SIGHS )
Stay safe .
Stay safe , sweetie .
( SIGHS )
( WHISPERING ) Okay .
MAN 1 ON RADIO : Both the people and the government wanted the Purge .
MAN 2 ON RADIO : The New Founding Fathers came into office ...
MAN 1 ON RADIO : Were voted into office by a country who wanted change ...
MAN 2 ON RADIO : This new regime took advantage of the nation 's fear .
( TURNS OFF RADIO )
I 'm glad we took the back roads .
The highways are probably a mess right now .
( SIGHING ) Yeah . We 'll be there in no time .
Yeah .
What are you looking at ?
Nothing . Just , you know , stuff .
Are you okay ?
Yeah . I 'm fine .
You sure ?
You don 't need to keep asking me .
My name is Donald Talbot .
Our regime was voted into office nine years ago .
And the first order of business
was to deal with the epidemic of crime
that was plaguing this nation .
The answer was the Purge .
( INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS )
You need some protection tonight ? You need something ?
Hey , man , we running out of ...
Hey , that Purge tonight , y 'all know what time it is .
Hitting them in the face ain 't gonna work no more .
You need something powerful .
How you doing , buddy ?
Use your hands , man . Just use your hands . Don 't even worry about it .
Hey , sweetheart , how you doing ? How you doing ?
You gonna need something for protection tonight ?
- No . No , I 'm good . I 'm good . - UZI ? Beretta ?
Look , on the cheap-cheap .
Or a blade to cut your man 's throat ? Whatever you need .
We take any kind of payment .
( DOGS BARKING AT DISTANCE )
Eva !
- Hey , Diego . - What 's up , girl ? How you doing ?
- Good . How you doing ? - Yeah ? Everything 's great ?
No , it 's not great . I 'm tired ...
Oh , it could be better .
Take me up there with you tonight . Get a little protection .
You know what I 'm saying ?
- Come on , now . - I 'm cool , Diego . I 'm good .
You sure you don 't want no protection ?
- Huh ? - No , thanks , Diego .
( CHUCKLING ) I 'm the man for the job . You know what I mean ?
CARMELO : We 've lost our souls to attain this peace .
We no longer worship at the altar of Christ ,
Muhammad , Yahweh .
We worship at the altar of Smith Wesson .
We , the people , know not what we do .
Horseshit . Where 'd you find this lunatic ?
I saw his protest posters all around the neighborhood .
He lives here , Papa . He 's just like us .
Now , shush . Please listen . He 's not a lunatic . ( CHUCKLING )
The Purge is not about containing crime to one night ,
and cleansing our souls by releasing aggression .
It 's about one thing . Money .
- Who dies tonight ? The poor . - ( SIGHING )
We can 't afford to protect ourselves .
That 's enough . I can 't listen to this crap .
He 's as full of shit as they are .
No , he 's right . Come on . They 're keeping the population down
by getting rid of people like us to save money .
- Talk is cheap , Cali . - Mmm-hmm .
He may be right , but he won 't do anything about it .
EVA : Home .
( KEYS JANGLING )
( EXHALES )
Hey , Daddy .
Don 't " hey , Daddy " me . Where have you been ?
We 're less than two hours until commencement ,
- and you 're out gallivanting . - ( SIGHING )
Gallivanting ? I was picking up your medicine .
Even worse . A waste of time and money .
Christ , Eva , I told you not to get this stuff .
EVA : I 'm tired of listening to this every day .
It does nothing ... I 'm not taking it !
- You 're taking your medicine . - I 'm not taking it ! No , I 'm not !
- Yes , you are ! - I 'm not taking it . You 're taking it back .
Oh , my God , really ?
( STAMMERING ) Can we stop ?
Look , Papa , maybe it doesn 't do anything , but can you just take it ?
For me ?
( SIGHS )
Okay .
( SIGHS ) We 'll lockdown and then we 'll eat after commencement .
Count me out .
I 'm gonna take a long nap , and don 't bother me .
I 'm gonna try to sleep through this godforsaken holiday .
Look , I 'm sorry I 'm so grumpy , girls .
I hate this night .
Please , forgive me .
( SIGHS )
( CHUCKLES )
EVA : You drive me crazy .
( SNIFFLES )
Uh ...
Make sure you lockdown everything .
I 'll take care of my room .
I love you both .
Very much .
I know .
That was weird .
It must be the night .
Yeah .
( SNIFFS )
I 'm gonna take a quick shower , and then we 'll lockdown .
Okay , wait . How did things go with Mrs. Crawley ?
- Did you get the raise ? - ( EXHALES DEEPLY )
God , what a bitch .
Well , did you at least make a good argument ?
Did you say everything that we practiced ?
I 'm sorry , baby .
Yeah .
- ( LIZ MUMBLING ) - ( MACHINE BEEPING )
I want to tell her , Shane .
Hey , did you hear me ?
I said I wanna tell your sister ...
Yeah , I heard you .
I just don 't feel like telling her .
Why ?
Because as soon as you say it out loud to another person ,
then it 's irreversible .
Do you have the keys ?
- Yeah . - ( KEYS JANGLING )
Handy ?
Right here .
Can you unlock the car , please ?
It 's unlocked .
No , it 's not .
There .
( BELLOWS )
Let 's just get in the car .
What the fuck was that all about ?
I don 't know . He didn 't tell me .
You know , we don 't have a whole lot of time before commencement , Shane .
All right . ( STAMMERING ) We 'll be fine , I promise .
( KNOCK ON DOOR )
Yeah .
I 've been calling . Why didn 't you pick up ?
What do you want ?
( SIGHS )
You can 't go out there . You know how dangerous it is ...
You need to go . You need to leave .
It 's late .
Don 't do this .
It won 't make you feel any better .
Go with your new husband ,
and your new family .
Leave .
( WHISPERING ) Just stay safe .
( SIGHS )
You , too . ( SIGHS )
( WATER TRICKLING )
CARMELO : Whatever happened to " Give me your needy ,
" your tired ,
" your huddled masses yearning to breathe free " ?
The redistribution of wealth upward
through killing has to stop .
We must pick up arms .
This year , we will fight back !
Jeez , that guy freaked me out .
Did not see him coming .
I thought we decided it was irreversible .
No , you often decide things on your own ,
and then pretend that they were a joint decision .
You often agree with me ,
and then a week later say ,
- " I don 't remember doing that . " - ( SCOFFS )
So , you 're calling me a liar ?
And you 're calling me a bully .
Just say you changed your mind ,
not that we didn 't come to a joint decision .
This is the exact ...
See , this is exactly why we need to tell your sister
that we 're separating .
You 're right , it 'll make it real ,
but I think we need to make it real .
Maybe I don 't wanna make it real .
- ( BANGING AND SQUEAKING ) - Whoa , whoa , whoa .
What the hell is that ?
The power steering 's gone .
What do you mean " the power steering 's gone " ?
( STAMMERS ) I don 't know . There 's something wrong with the car .
- Can you pull over ? - I 'm trying .
( ENGINE SPUTTERING )
Shit .
Try it again .
( CLICKING )
It 's dead .
( TIRES SQUEAL )
( ENGINE REVS )
WOMAN : ( ON RADIO ) The sixth Annual Purge will begin in 45 minutes .
( SIGHS )
Just in case .
Yeah .
Hey .
We 're gonna be fine .
Just like every year .
Yeah . ( CHUCKLES )
I 'll pay three times as much if you just come out here ...
No , no , no . I don 't care about the car . We just need a ride .
- It 's ... Hello ? - Whoa , whoa ! Hey !
Hey ! Whoa , whoa , whoa !
( BOTH SHOUTING )
- Stop ! - Shit .
Please !
- Shane , we can 't be stuck outside . - I know . I know .
We 're downtown . Everyone comes downtown to Purge .
Hey , hey . Don 't worry .
We 'll figure something out , I promise .
( LIQUID DRIPPING )
Is that coming from our car ?
Oh , shit .
( BIKES APPROACHING )
( WHISPERING ) He cut those wires , Shane .
Yeah .
( PANTS ) We need to run .
Yeah , go , go .
NEWSREADER : News 13 wishes anyone
who is not participating in this year 's Purge a safe evening
and for those releasing the beast , a successful cleanse .
Good luck .
- ( BEEPING ) - Should I get Papa ?
( SIGHS ) He hates this . Let him sleep .
FEMALE VOICE : This is not a test .
This is your Emergency Broadcast System
announcing the commencement of The Annual Purge
sanctioned by the US Government .
Weapons of Class 4 and lower
have been authorized for use during the Purge .
All other weapons are restricted .
Government officials of ranking 10 have been granted immunity ...
Commencing at the siren , any and all crime , including murder ,
will be legal for 12 continuous hours .
Police , fire and emergency medical services
will be unavailable until tomorrow morning at 7 : 00 a.m.
when the Purge concludes .
Blessed be our New Founding Fathers , and America , a nation reborn .
- May God be with you all . - Let 's go this way . Let 's just go .
( SIREN BLARING )
( EXHALES )
( SIGHS )
( SIGHS DEEPLY )
( BLARING CONTINUES )
( DOG BARKING )
( YELLING )
( DOOR BUZZES )
( THUDDING )
( MAN GRUNTING )
( GUNSHOTS )
( MAN WHOOPING )
( GUNSHOTS CONTINUE )
( TIRES SQUEALING )
Come on . Come on . Come on . Do you think they 're still after us ?
- I have no idea . - Okay .
- Let 's just get out of here . - ( MAN YELLING )
- Oh , God ! - Let 's get out of here . Go !
( HEAVY BREATHING )
( MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY )
LIZ : Where do we go ?
Here , get in this . Get in this !
We 'll just hide in here . Come on .
( BOTH PANTING )
- Go . - ( SCREAMS ) Oh , God !
Let 's just get out of here .
Come on , come on . You 're good .
( MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY )
( ENGINE STARTS )
SHANE : Fuck , it 's them .
We gotta move , we gotta move . We gotta move .
( DISTANT GUNSHOT )
( CUTLERY CLATTERS )
I 'm gonna go get Papa for dinner .
He said don 't bother him .
Yeah . I just wanna see if he 's awake .
CALI : Mom !
- What ? What is it ? - Mom , come here !
What 's wrong ?
Where 's Papa ?
Look at this .
PAPA RICO : " Dearest Eva and Cali ,
" my greatest heartache is seeing the two girls I love so much
" struggling in this world .
" I am dying , you know this .
" I 'll be a martyr for a wealthy family tonight .
" They paid me for this service .
" $ 100,000 will be transferred into your accounts , my darlings .
" Take their money .
- " Survive the night and live a safe life . - ( INDISTINCT )
" I love you . "
ALL : Blessed be America , a nation reborn .
I don 't understand .
It 's how the wealthy Purge , baby . ( INHALES SHARPLY )
They buy poor and sick people ,
and they take them in their homes
and they kill them where they 're safe .
( WHISPERING ) Oh , my God .
It 's just like Carmelo said .
Why would Papa do that ? I don 't understand why he would do that .
( SNIFFLES )
Okay , he must have left something
that could tell us where he went .
- Cali . Cali . - ( SNIFFLES ) Like his phone . We should call his phone .
We could stop him .
- EVA : Cali ... - CALI : Okay , that 's fine .
We can do something about this . I don 't know what ,
- but we can still do something about it . - Cali , stop .
Just stop . He 's gone .
- He 's gone . - ( SNIFFLES )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( SNIFFLES )
( SOBS )
( LOUD RUMBLING )
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
( LOUD THUDDING )
( DOOR BUZZES )
( EXHALES ) What is this ?
Who are they ? It looks like an army .
( WHISPERING ) I have no idea .
- ( EXPLOSION ) - ( BOTH GASP )
( GLASS SHATTERS )
- It 's them . - No , it can 't be them .
They haven 't even come inside yet .
That was right in the other room . ( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( DOOR OPENS )
DIEGO : Eva !
I 'm here to protect you .
Protect you from me . ( CHUCKLES )
( WHISPERING ) Mom , where 's the gun ?
It 's in the kitchen .
( SNIFFLES )
( WHISTLING )
Where you hiding , bitch ?
Don 't you know that you gotta be polite to people in this society ?
Because if not ,
this is what happens tonight !
Diego , don 't come back here . We have guns and we will shoot you .
Cali ?
That you ?
Oh , I got a little bonus .
- ( WOMAN SCREAMS ) - Got a little package deal .
But I 'll tell you what , tonight I 'm gonna release the beast ,
on the both of you fucking lame bitches !
It 's my right ,
granted to me by the New Found Fathers !
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( CHUCKLING )
You thought your little weak-ass protection
was gonna keep me out or what , huh ?
Let me tell you something .
Not with the barricade buster .
Saved up a lot of pennies for this bitch , let me tell you .
Diego , don 't you hear those people in our building ?
Now you shut the fuck up !
The only thing you gotta be concerned with is who wants to go first .
- ( SOBBING ) - Huh ?
Who ?
Leave my daughter alone .
CALI : Mom , don 't .
- You can do what you want to me , Diego . - ( CALI SNIFFLES )
I will . Trust me when I tell you , I will .
You better prepare yourself tonight ,
'cause tonight , it 's motherfucking on , bitch .
That 's right , because it 's Diego 's night !
It 's my night to motherfucking Purge !
My fucking time !
( MAN PLEADING )
( GUNSHOTS FIRING )
( MAN GRUNTING )
( ENGINE REVVING )
( HOOTING )
Every fucking day , you pass me by in the hallway ,
like I ain 't shit !
Well , now , that shit fucking changes ! I change shit !
I beg you , please !
- Oh , fucking beg , bitch ! - Please ...
You fucking beg ! Beg !
- Please ! I 'm saying please ! - ( CALI SOBBING )
Beg , yeah .
- Don 't touch my daughter , please . - ( CHUCKLING )
EVA : Please , leave her alone .
- Let me hear you say please . - She 's got nothing to do with it .
- Please . - ( THUDDING )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
What 's that ? Huh ?
- Is it your father ? - I don 't know .
- Is that your father ? - CALI : Please , please .
I like that .
( GROANING )
- ( THUDS ) - ( GASPS )
Come on , motherfucker ! You want some , too ?
Come and get it !
- Where you at ? - ( GUN COCKS )
( GRUNTS )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( WHISPERING ) Is it him ?
( STIFLED SOBBING )
( BOTH GASP )
GUNMAN 1 : This is what he was looking for tonight .
Let 's bring these two downstairs .
GUNMAN 2 : Big Daddy , we have two for your personal Purge .
Bringing them down now .
( SCREAMING )
Get off me !
( GRUNTS )
( GRUNTING )
Cali !
( EVA SCREAMING )
( INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER )
( WOMAN SOBBING )
( SCREAMING )
CALI : No ! No !
EVA : Cali !
Oh , God , no ! Let go !
No ! ( GRUNTING )
Get the fuck off me !
- EVA : Please ! - ( GRUNTING )
Leave my daughter alone !
( BOTH SCREAMING )
( INDISTINCT )
EVA : Please , don 't . Please , please , please .
( CALI GROANING )
( EVA AND CALI STRUGGLING )
Just drive . Just drive . Just drive .
( GRUNTING )
Get off of me !
Mom !
( POUNDING )
Just fucking drive .
Please ! Let my daughter go !
Cali !
No , fucking ...
Mom !
( GUN COCKS )
( STRUGGLING )
( PANTING )
( DOOR BUZZES )
- I don 't know . - They were right behind us .
What the fuck is that ?
- Shit . - What do we do ?
SHANE : Here , get in . It 's open .
No !
Get off !
( GROANING )
( GROANS )
What is going on out there ?
We 're safe , we 're safe . We 're in here . We 're good .
( SIGHS )
- Let 's go . - ( BREATHING HEAVILY )
- SERGEANT : Hey ! Out of the car ! - LIZ : No , no , no !
Please ! Please , don 't !
Get out of the car , or I will shoot !
We 're not Purging ! We don 't have any weapons ! Please .
- I will shoot you ! - LIZ : Please don 't shoot !
- SERGEANT : Move out of the car now ! - SHANE : No , we 're not armed !
- SERGEANT : Get out of the car ! - LIZ : We can 't ! They 're after us !
Wait , wait , wait . We have to go ! We have to go , please !
We don 't wanna hurt anybody !
- LIZ : Please , don 't ... - Shut up ! Shut up !
Hands up , and shut your mouth !
- Please . Please . - LIZ : Hands are up !
SHANE : Thank you , thank you .
SERGEANT : Get in , get in , get in .
- Shane ? - What ?
- They 're coming . - We gotta go !
Over there , too !
There 's people over here , too ! You gotta move , you gotta move !
Please , go ! Please .
SERGEANT : Shut up !
LIZ : Drive !
( GASPS )
( TIRES SCREECHING )
( SCREAMS )
SHANE : He 's shooting at the motorcycles . They 're turning !
They 're not following us .
They 're gone , they 're gone . They 're all gone .
- Are you sure ? - SHANE : Yeah , yeah , yeah .
Yeah , there 's no one there !
Are you okay , baby ?
Yeah , I 'm fine . Are you ?
( SIGHS ) Yeah .
Sir , are you okay ?
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
You . What was that army doing in your building ?
- Why were they after you ? - I don 't know .
Why were they after you ?
I don 't know ! I don 't know .
- Why are you in the streets ? - Our car just broke down .
We 're not out to Purge . We don 't wanna hurt anybody .
- Are you armed ? - No ! No !
What about you ? What were you doing outside ?
Oh , God .
Look , Mom ... Mom , it 's okay . We 're safe now .
( WHISPERING ) No , we 're not .
Sir , where are we going ?
Honestly , anywhere but here is fine with me . Just ...
( ENGINE SPUTTERS )
God damn it .
Maybe nowhere .
( DISTANT SHOUTING )
Whoever 's in that truck was using armor piercing bullets .
The car is dead .
So , that 's it . We 're stuck outside on Purge Night .
What are we gonna do ?
Can we just hide in here ? We have seven hours until morning .
There 's hunters out there with dogs .
Sooner or later , they 're gonna find you .
But you do what you want .
- You 're on your own now . - Huh ?
- What ? - Whoa !
Whoa , what do you mean , we 're on our own ?
I should never have gotten involved . It 's none of my business .
Okay , but you did , so it is your business now , all right ?
So , what are we all going to do ?
Take this . It 's loaded . Take it .
- Take it . - You 're just giving us guns ?
Where are you going ?
I got somewhere to be before the sun comes up .
I can 't take you with me , you 'll slow me down .
So , you 're really just gonna leave us here ?
( SIGHS )
Stay off the streets . Find somewhere to go .
Please , take us with you .
We are not the kind of people who will survive tonight .
SHANE : Let him go , all right ? He doesn 't wanna help .
- Shane , shut up ! - SHANE : Let him ...
Why did you save us if you were just gonna leave us here to die ?
Please , help us !
EVA : Wait ! I can get you a car .
I have a friend in the city not far from here .
I 've worked with her for years .
If you get us there safely ,
you can take her car and do what you have to do .
Where does she live ?
Third and Bryant .
- Will she give me her car ? - Mmm-hmm .
Are you sure ?
Mmm-hmm .
Make sure .
( SIGHS )
Okay .
Hey , it 's Eva .
Listen , we 're in trouble .
That was a real dick move , you know ?
Walking away and then coming back .
EVA : Thank you so much . Thank you . Okay , we 'll be there really soon .
And listen , I need your car as well .
I 'll explain when I get there , is that okay ?
What are you looking for ?
Snipers .
Thank you so much . Okay .
Uh , she lives with her parents . They 're happy to have us .
If you can get us to her place safely , the car is yours .
Can she help us , too ?
Yeah .
Thank you .
She 'll give me the car ?
All right , I 'm gonna help you get to your friend 's , but I want that car .
I know .
All right , you listen to what I say . You stay close .
You slow me down , I cut you all loose , you understand ?
Yeah . Yeah .
Okay . Let 's go .
( GUNSHOTS )
WOMAN : I 'm doing God 's work .
He uses an earthquake , a virus .
( GUNSHOTS )
Population under control .
The masses nourish and flourish .
I am that virus tonight .
I am a one-woman fucking plague
and you 're all in my path !
I am the Holy Trinity . Oh , I am the Holy Trinity .
I am the Holy Trinity .
I am the Father Fucker , Son of a Bitch , and Holy Shit !
When I move , you move , understand ? Stay close , don 't stray .
- Okay ? - Yeah .
And my MP-9 silver-tipped Auto Magnum .
The right arm of the free world and the left hand of God !
Go !
In flaming fire , I take the heads of them that know not God .
We 're gonna go down Fifth . Your friend 's building is close .
Go through the business district , stay away from the gangs downtown .
( MAN SCREAMING )
LIZ : Wait a minute .
( BIKES APPROACHING )
( MAN SCREAMING )
( ENGINE REVVING )
( MAN SCREAMS )
Stay back , stay back .
No ! Please , don 't !
( SCREAMING ) No ! No !
What are they doing ? Where are they taking him ?
It 's not our business .
Those are the guys that were after us .
SERGEANT : It 's okay . It 's not our problem .
We 're gonna have people in front of us , and we 're gonna have people behind us .
As long as we move , we 'll be fine .
We 're gonna cross Banks .
No , no , no , that 's the long way .
It 's gonna be much quicker if we go down here .
( SCREAMING )
( GRUNTS )
LIZ : What is this ?
Get it off of me , I 'm stuck !
It 's a trap . It 's a trap . We don 't have time .
- Move away , I gotta shoot it . - What ?
SHANE : What ? You 're gonna what ?
I 'm gonna shoot it . Move !
- LIZ : What ? - Okay .
( SCREAMS )
Shoot it ! Shoot the cable !
( SCREAMING )
( GRUNTS )
Shoot it !
Shane , hurry up !
SERGEANT : Get up , get up !
( GROANS )
- Move ! - LIZ : Okay , let 's go !
( GUNSHOTS )
( WOMAN SCREAMS )
AUTOMATED VOICE : There are six hours remaining in this year 's ...
( STATIC AND SHOUTING )
CARMELO : The NFFA pigs are wrong . They 're fucking wrong !
Profit-making is not the essence of democracy .
Wake up , people . Wake up ! It 's time to take a stand .
Tonight , we write our message in blood .
Their blood !
It 's so quiet here .
SERGEANT : The business district 's always quiet on Purge Night .
The banks move their money , so no one 's ever down here .
Let 's go .
( DISTANT SCREAMING )
( WHISPERING ) Stop .
We don 't even know your names .
I 'm Liz , and this is Shane .
Hi .
Eva . My daughter , Cali .
It 's nice to officially meet you on this shitty night .
Yeah .
Is anyone else kind of curious about this guy ?
I 'm just glad that he 's out here with us .
Yeah , me , too .
But we all got stuck out here , and he chose to be .
That means he 's Purging .
( WHISPERING ) Hey . Let 's go .
Are you saying that we shouldn 't trust him ?
He saved our lives .
All I 'm saying is that he 's out here
armed to the teeth , on Purge Night , voluntarily .
That means he 's trying to do something nasty .
I can hear you .
Sorry . Just go .
Hey , are you doing okay ?
( WHISPERING ) Yeah . Yeah . It 's gonna be fine .
I 'm gonna go talk to him .
Cali .
- What 's your name ? - Shh .
You 're good with guns .
I 'm guessing you 're either a cop or a criminal , huh ?
And I 'm guessing you 're either a pain in my ass or a pain in my ass .
You 're out here to do it , aren 't you ?
To Purge ? That 's what you have to do later on , right ?
What are you gonna do ?
Stop .
New rules . You shut up .
All of you , shut up .
I 'm gonna stop talking because you 're being an asshole , okay ?
Not because you told me to shut up .
Cali .
Hey , hey , hey .
Okay .
Oh , my God .
SHANE : " Here hangs stockbroker David Neustadter . He stole our pensions .
" Now , he 's gone . "
Maybe David deserved it .
Just a bad joke .
What the hell is that ?
Is that tear gas ?
Smoke canister .
Stay close , stay close , stay close .
- Help me ! - ( SCREAMING )
Grab him ! Get off her !
Get off her !
( GRUNTING )
We were just doing our duty .
Is she okay ?
- He scared the shit out of me . - All right . You 're okay , though .
( LIZ BREATHING HEAVILY )
SHANE : Just breathe . Just breathe . Just take a breath .
CALI : Look at his uniform .
This is one of the bastards who came into our building .
And that looks like their truck .
All right , stay here . Stay here .
MAN : ( OVER PA ) Truck 3 , come in .
Come in , please .
- Come on . - Come on , let 's go , let 's go .
Just stay together . Let 's go .
Oh , Jesus .
MAN : ( OVER PA ) Truck 3 , please respond !
Go check the cab , see if this thing 's working .
- Stay alert . Stay alert . - ( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( GRUNTS )
Go ahead . Go . Go , go , go .
CALI : This is some high-tech shit .
Yo , somebody spent a lot of money
trying to do some heavy-duty Purging .
Look at this . They 're accessing the city 's traffic cams .
Looking for targets , I guess .
Traffic cams are controlled by the government .
How did they get into these ?
I mean , who are these people ?
Maybe you just answered your own question .
Look at this . Seventh Street .
Is that your building ?
Yeah , but why is it all red ?
You 're being targeted for something , along with all these other buildings .
Here , here . All over the city .
EVA : All around the projects .
Maybe you were right , Cali .
Look , I 'm telling you , this is the New Founding Fathers .
- The government ... - SHANE : The truck is fucked .
- No good ? - No , the engine 's all blown out or something .
Hey , look at this .
That 's Carmelo 's mark , Mom .
I told Papa he was the real deal .
His group took these fuckers out .
SERGEANT : Everybody got a weapon ?
Hey , grab this . Take the weapon . Go . Go !
- Go ! - Oh , shit , there 's another one .
Looks like an army . Come on .
Get down , let 's go .
( INDISTINCT SHOUTING )
( SQUEAKING )
( SCREAMS )
( MUFFLED GASP )
Take this .
Shh .
( GRUNTING )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
Come on .
( EXHALES DEEPLY )
Hey .
Why did you stop at our building ?
Why did you help us ?
Didn 't we establish a no-talking rule ?
People are getting killed all over the city .
Why did you stop for us ?
I saw you . You were putting up a hell of a fight .
( CHUCKLES )
You reminded me of someone .
Who ?
Look , Purging , no matter what the reason , is wrong .
Killing doesn 't help anything .
It doesn 't heal someone .
Enough . Enough .
Go back with your mommy .
Go .
( SIGHS )
There 's no air in here . ( INHALES SHARPLY )
( EXHALES )
Come over here . Put this on .
- I don 't need that . - Put it on , I said .
- I said I don 't need it . - Put it on .
Put your arm through here .
Now , hopefully , you won 't need it .
Let 's move .
( CLANGING )
- EVA : What was that ? - SERGEANT : Shh .
( GRUNTING )
SERGEANT : There 's no threat .
They 're just trying to make it through the night .
Keep moving .
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
Hey , are you okay ?
I just wanna get out of here .
( VEHICLES APPROACHING )
( INDISTINCT YELLING )
Oh , shit !
Move !
SHANE : Go ! Come on !
( YELLING )
( GRUNTS )
Run ! Move !
( INDISTINCT SHOUTING )
( GROANS )
Move !
( ALL PANTING )
( SHOUTING )
( GRUNTS )
Get up ! Get up ! Come on !
Get up , get up , get up !
Mom , we have to go right now !
SERGEANT : Move it , move it ! Move !
( EVIL LAUGHING )
( SCREAMING )
Go , go !
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( SCREAMING )
Up , up , up !
( SCREAMS )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
We 're not gonna make it . Fuck it .
Shane !
- What are you doing ? - SHANE : Get down !
- What do we do ? - Just shoot ! Just shoot !
( GROANS )
Shane !
( SERGEANT PANTING )
( GRUNTS )
- Oh , my God . - I 'm fine , I 'm fine , I 'm fine !
Just keep shooting . Just keep shooting . Go ! Go !
( GROANS )
( MAN SCREAMING )
- All right . You 're okay . - ( BREATHING HEAVILY )
Stay here . Give me this .
I 'm so sorry . I 'm so sorry , I 'm so sorry .
I was just so scared .
( ALL PANTING )
You 're bleeding .
- I cut it on the platform . It 's fine . - We 'll help you . Just tell us ...
I said , it 's fine !
Get up . Get up .
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
EVA : What 's taking them so long ?
Help ! He 's been shot ! I have no idea how bad .
( SHANE GROANS )
- SERGEANT : Open up . - LIZ : We 're gonna be fine , okay ?
Call your friend . Tell her we 're close . We 're gonna get him up .
Okay . Look at me . Look at me , Shane . Yeah ?
One , two , three . Get him up .
- LIZ : Let 's go ! - ( GROANING )
AUTOMATED VOICE : There are four hours and 30 minutes
remaining in this year 's Purge .
- SERGEANT : Go ! Just don 't worry ! Go ! Come on , come on ! - ( PANTING )
Keep moving !
Go ! Don 't slow down ! Keep moving !
It 's right up ahead .
Come on !
Cali ! Slow down !
( GRUNTING )
Hey , look , that 's her building !
She said to meet around the back .
( WHIRRING )
MAN : ( OVER PA ) We have a target match on the civilians who attacked Truck 2 .
EVA : She said , " Meet us around the back . "
Tanya ! Let us in !
It 's Eva and Cali !
Holy shit ! You guys look like hell .
Come on , come on , hurry up . Get in here . Hurry up !
- EVA : Thank you . - I don 't like being out here . Come on .
( LOCK CLICKS )
SERGEANT : All right .
- Bullet went right through . - ( SHANE GROANS )
I can 't believe you guys went through all that stuff .
It 's just insane !
Get him to the hospital first thing after this is over .
- Yeah . - You 'll be okay .
It 's gonna hurt like a son of a bitch , but you 're gonna be okay .
- ( EXHALES DEEPLY ) Thanks . - I can 't thank you enough .
That 's what you get for being a hero .
( CHUCKLES )
( SIGHS )
- I need the car . - I know .
Come on , everybody . Eat , drink !
TANYA : Yes , I recommend drinking .
It 's the best way to get through the evening .
And the food is delicious .
My mother 's a wonderful cook .
My sister 's a testament to that .
What the hell does that mean ?
TANYA : That she 's a good cook !
You know , you didn 't have to go this far . Just having us here was really enough .
You guys have had a terrible night .
Get some food in your system ,
and we 'll get through this together .
LORRAINE : Excuse me .
Cali ?
TANYA : I can 't believe nobody 's drinking with me .
What about you , tough guy ?
Want a drink ?
No , thanks .
Okay .
You 're really going back out there ?
- ( DOOR OPENS ) - TANYA : Mmm !
Relax ! It 's my father and my brother-in-law . He 's the super .
They were just checking the building . It 's all good .
Everyone , please don 't mind my husband 's clothes .
He 's not Purging .
He just thought it was a crazy idea
to go out and see what 's happening tonight .
Yeah , I chickened out .
No way I was going out there .
- I don 't know what the hell I was thinking . - ( LORRAINE CHUCKLES )
Thank God he came to his senses . I mean , look at him .
He would 've been the laughingstock of the neighborhood .
That 's not very nice , Lorraine .
I 'm sorry . I didn 't mean for it to be mean .
It 's not mean , it 's just true .
( GUN COCKS )
How 's everything , Daddy ?
It 's all good , baby .
The building 's locked down and good .
It 's quiet .
I see you had a rough go of it , my friend .
- Oh , yeah . - BARNEY : Relax .
Make yourself at home . You 're safe here .
We are anti-Purge in this household .
( CHUCKLES ) Speak for yourself , Daddy .
What does that mean ?
I could think of a couple situations where Purging could be the answer .
- Like when ? - TANYA : I 'm not telling .
I 'm just saying , don 't piss me off , bitch .
- KATHERINE : Uh , please excuse my daughter . - LIZ : No , it 's fine .
And , please , if there 's anything else you need , just ask .
I could use a clean shirt .
BARNEY : Down the hall , second door on the left .
Top drawer of the bureau . What 's mine is yours .
Okay . Excuse me , too .
I 'm gonna go to the little girl 's room
'cause this wine is going right through me .
KATHERINE : Come on , everyone , please eat and drink .
Come on . Honey ?
( TANYA COUGHS )
REPORTER : This is News 10 reporting on a lively Purge Night across the country .
We have riots in East Los Angeles ,
as well as record participation in Pittsburgh .
( WHISPERING ) He wasn 't lying .
This shit hurts .
Aw , I 'm sorry .
( SIGHS )
You scared the shit out of me .
I thought I was losing you .
But I still think we should tell your sister .
( STUTTERS )
You 're an asshole .
- I 'm sorry . - That 's not funny .
- I 'm sorry . - No , I got shot .
Oh , are you gonna use this excuse for the rest of our lives ?
- Well , at least the rest of the night . - ( CHUCKLING ) Okay .
All right , people , let 's change the atmosphere up in here .
No more Purge news . No more nothing depressing .
Let 's put on some music , and let 's just liven it up a little bit , right ?
- ( MUSIC PLAYING ) - Come on , you want to dance ?
Why not ?
Liven up the party , come on .
Let 's dance . ( CHUCKLING ) Let 's dance !
Okay , I gotta go . I need the car .
- ( WHISPERING ) I know . - You trust these people ?
Because your friend likes to drink ,
and she 's taking pills back there .
Yeah , she 's pretty wild .
But we 'll be okay . She 's a good friend .
What ? You don 't wanna do it ? What ?
Lorraine , do you care if we dance ?
She doesn 't even care . She 's not even paying attention .
Now he 's ... Look at him .
- ( CHUCKLING ) He 's asleep . - He is .
I don 't know how to thank you .
Okay , if you can just tell her I need the car right now ,
that would be really great .
I know what you 're doing tonight .
You 're going out there to kill someone who wronged you .
You believe in this night , don 't you ?
I think you should just take care of your daughter .
She 's special , and you 're very lucky .
And I need the car .
There is no car .
What ?
I 'm sorry , they don 't have a car .
But we needed you .
And I needed the car .
I did what I had to . I did it for my daughter .
I was doing this for my son .
And I trusted you .
You have no idea what you might have taken away from me tonight .
- Hey . - Hey .
Look , I know you 're angry with my mother ,
but I really think you should just stay here .
Just wait out the night with us , okay ?
Look , I heard you say that you 're doing it for your son .
Now , I don 't know him ,
but I 'm sure he would not want you to do whatever it is that you 're going to do .
- Bye , Cali . - Please , come on , you 're safe here .
- Get out of my way . - Please , just ...
I gotta go . Goodbye .
- Stay here . It 's fine . - Get out of the way .
Get back !
No ! ( SCREAMS )
RODDY : Lorraine !
KATHERINE : What are you doing ?
Tanya ! Tanya !
( GRUNTING )
RODDY : Lorraine !
What 've you done ? What are you doing , Lorraine ?
Jesus Christ , she 's dead .
RODDY : You killed your sister ! She 's your sister !
Lorraine ! What are you doing ?
You know what I 'm doing .
I read all your emails , you cheating motherfuckers .
You both deserve to die !
( SCREAMS )
Okay , Lorraine ! Lorraine , stop !
- No ! - Get back , get back . Back up , back up !
I 'm sorry , okay ? I 'm sorry .
- What the fuck are you doing ? - Lorraine .
If you shoot me , you shoot this woman .
Just let her go !
RODDY : You don 't wanna do that !
Lorraine , I 'm sorry . I didn 't mean anything .
I didn 't mean it . She hasn 't done anything to you .
Okay ? So , cut this out !
Fuck you ! This is my right , granted to me by my government .
( BOTH SCREAMING )
Leave him alone ! He 's mine !
Door , now . Go .
( SCREAMS )
Door ! Go !
Door , door , door !
Now !
Move , move , move !
( GROANS )
- SERGEANT : Go , go ! - ( CALI PANTING )
I can 't believe Tanya 's dead .
What do we do now ? Where do we go ?
( PANTING )
( GRUNTING )
Are you gonna leave us now ?
What ?
( VEHICLES APPROACHING )
You 've gotta be fucking kidding me .
- Shh ! - How did they find us ?
Stay here .
Don 't move !
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
Do you think he 's gonna come back ?
What do we do if he doesn 't ?
( EXHALES DEEPLY )
BIG DADDY : Come on , guys . Let 's go , okay ?
We don 't have all night . I want this building surrounded .
He 's here .
I know it , and I want him . Understood ?
He shot me .
He shot half my team . I want him dead .
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( WHISPERING ) Come on , come on , come on .
BIG DADDY : And I want the two women he saved .
They 're mine .
I want them alive .
Please come back .
They found us . Move fast , now . Come on .
Move now . We have 30 seconds .
Over the fence , fast . Now . Go !
Next . Come on , come on , come on .
( FENCE JANGLING )
( GRUNTING )
Look at me . You go , you get over that fence , you run .
You don 't stop . You run for your life .
Do you understand ? You don 't fucking wait for me .
Go . Go , go , go !
Fuck !
( WHIRRING )
( GRUNTS )
( GROANING )
( ENGINE REVVING )
( SERGEANT BREATHING HEAVILY )
( SOBBING )
How did you find us ?
No , Cali , no .
We got lucky .
I mean , we was roaming around out there all night .
Just picking up the people who got away from those badass trucks .
( CHUCKLES )
We get their scraps .
Why haven 't you just killed us already ?
We 're not Purging tonight .
We don 't need to kill anyone .
We just need money . Right , bro ?
Money !
( VEHICLE APPROACHING )
- ( BRAKES SCREECHING ) - MAN : Whoa !
All right , let 's go .
Let 's go , let 's go , let 's go !
Come on , come on , let 's go , let 's go !
LIZ : No , no , no !
Who the fuck are they ?
What the fuck are you doing to us ?
I need my money , man . Let 's go , let 's do this .
- What are they doing ? - ( SERGEANT SHUSHING )
- MAN : It 's all there . - Yeah !
Let 's go ! Let 's go , move !
( INDISTINCT SHOUTING )
( GRUNTS )
- MAN : Get in there ! - CALI : No !
- EVA : Cali ? - Mom !
Get up the stairs , now .
( GRUNTS )
( GROANS )
MAN : Get up ! Get up !
Get on your knees . Get down ! Get down !
- Get on your knees . - ( GRUNTS )
On your knees !
( BREATHES HEAVILY )
- Where are we ? What is this ? - Shh .
MAN : If you move or speak ,
you will be shot .
WOMAN : Ladies and gentlemen , the next batch has just arrived .
Let 's take a look , shall we ?
( DOOR BUZZING )
( PIANO PLAYING )
Quite an impressive lot , isn 't it ?
Ladies and gentlemen , since this is the last Purge of the evening ,
the entry price will be $ 200,000 .
Mr. Lockhart !
And his wonderful wife , Lauren .
Fantastic .
The Hanover sisters !
Ah !
I 've been waiting all evening for your participation .
Fantastic .
And I assume you brought your signature blades .
All right , one spot left . Anyone else ?
Mr. Hearst ! Oh , wonderful !
And will your handsome sons be joining you ?
- ( WHISPERING ) What do you say , guys ? - Yeah , let 's do it .
Ladies and gentlemen , this will be Charles and Tom 's first .
I am so happy that you have this to share together .
Oh , and one last reminder .
The weapons rack is stocked with the latest and the greatest .
And my personal favorite
is the Mauser Elite SSX Double Barrel .
It has a delicate trigger ,
and smoothest discharge .
It is so precise ,
- it 's as if God handcrafted it himself . - ( BREATHING HEAVILY )
Well , that will do it .
Purgers , please suit up .
Good luck .
Good luck . We 'll see you shortly on the hunting grounds .
Get up . Come on ! Get up ! Get up ! Get up !
MAN : Quit stalling !
Come on !
- Move your ass ! - CALI : Okay !
( INDISTINCT SHOUTING )
Move it ! Go !
- Move it ! - Get in there !
Stay close to me .
Follow me . Move .
Get down .
Get down , get down .
Wait .
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
SHANE : What is this ?
We 're being hunted .
SHANE : What ?
( INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS )
ALL : Blessed be the New Founding Fathers
for letting us Purge and cleanse our souls .
Blessed be America , a nation reborn .
All right , they 're here .
( INAUDIBLE )
( GUNSHOTS )
SERGEANT : They 're coming , and they got night vision .
I gotta take one of them down . If we can 't see , we 're dead .
We should come with you .
- No , no , no . I need you to stay here . - Don 't go . I 'm scared .
I 'm coming back , I 'm coming back . Stay here .
( SCREAMING )
- ( GUNSHOTS ) - ( MAN GRUNTING )
( GUNSHOTS )
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
MAN : No ! ( GROANS )
( GRUNTING )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( GASPS )
( BOTH GRUNTING )
( GROANING )
( GRUNTING )
( INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( GROANING )
( GRUNTS )
( ALL SCREAMING )
( ALL PANTING )
- Are you okay ? - Fine .
We only get two sets of eyes now , okay ? Put those on .
I took out four of these fuckers .
There 's three left .
It 's loaded . You point and you shoot .
Someone 's coming right at us .
Light him up .
( MAN GRUNTS )
( PANTING )
( BOTH PANTING )
SERGEANT : They 're going .
LIZ : They 're all gone .
- They 're leaving . - ( WHISPERING ) Get down , get down .
- ( ALL PANTING ) - Is it over ?
Stay down .
We need help right now .
They 've killed five people . They 've killed five of us .
LIZ : ( WHISPERING ) They 're gone .
What the fuck ?
What was that ?
There 's a whole fucking army .
I don 't have any more bullets .
Just hold my hand , baby .
( WHISPERING ) They 're not gonna let us out of here .
You make them earn it .
I 'm sorry for everything .
( PANTING )
- I love you . I need you to know that . - ( MACHINE GUN FIRING )
( GASPS )
No !
No . Okay . Come on .
( SOBBING )
Come on .
Okay .
It 's gonna be okay .
You 're okay .
( SOBBING )
Okay , okay .
( DISTANT EXPLOSIONS )
What is that ?
Oh , my God .
WOMAN : ( OVER SPEAKER ) The use of explosives
higher than Class 4 is prohibited on Purge Night .
You will be prosecuted .
( MEN SCREAMING )
The use of explosives higher than Class 4 is prohibited ...
The use of explosives higher than Class 4 is prohibited on Purge Night .
You will be prosecuted .
Do not fire ! We 're here to help you !
Take positions over there .
We need a firing line . Let 's go !
( GRUNTING )
Who the fuck are you ?
MAN : Nobody special .
Just some people who don 't necessarily agree with the Purge is all .
( GUNS FIRING )
You 're with Carmelo Johns .
( PANTING ) Yes .
CARMELO : Fuck the New Founding Fathers !
Fuck you !
Fuck your money ! And motherfuck the Purge !
- ( GUNS FIRING IN DISTANCE ) - Carmelo !
- We 're over here . - ( MAN GRUNTS )
I know you .
You once said that
the market mentality would no longer keep the American people stunted .
" We are outraged and we 're fighting back . "
- ( GUNS FIRING ) - ( MAN GRUNTING )
Nice to meet you , too , young lady .
There 's a lot of them out here .
( WHISPERING ) Yeah , well , there 's more of us .
We 're more pissed off .
It 's time for them to feel what it 's like .
Change only comes when their blood spills .
You might wanna get out of here . It 's about to get nasty .
( LIZ WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY )
SERGEANT : Hey .
We gotta go .
Look at me .
He 's gone .
Come on .
I wanna Purge .
Look , we 'll take care of her .
- ( GUN FIRING ) - ( MAN GRUNTS )
Are you sure ?
MAN : Go . We got it .
Come on .
I 'm sorry .
MAN : Here , take it . ( PANTING )
Get ready to bleed , rich bitches ! This is our time now !
( GUNS FIRING )
( TIRES SCREECHING )
Get out of the car .
Leave the keys and get out of the car . Get out of the car !
Oh ! Oh , God , no !
- No , don 't shoot me . No . No , don 't shoot me . - SERGEANT : Look at me !
- Please , don 't shoot me . - You don 't deserve to live , you piece of shit .
- ( WHIMPERING ) - You remember me , okay ? You remember me .
No !
Now , run .
- Run ! Run ! - ( WHIMPERS )
Faster !
CALI : Look , it 's almost over .
( PANTING ) No , there 's still time . I can make it .
I can make it .
MAN : ( OVER SPEAKER ) There isn 't much time left in this year 's Purge .
Get out there and make yourself better citizens .
God be with you all .
You want to tell us what we 're doing here ?
Do you see that house on the corner ?
The owner of that house killed my son 12 months ago .
( SERGEANT SIGHS )
Nicholas
was coming home from school ,
and he swerved off the road .
That bastard 's blood alcohol level was three times the legal limit ,
but , you know , he got off on a technicality , so ...
Him and his wife and his two little kids ,
well , they live in that house ,
happily ever after .
Two weeks ago , I came here
and I disabled his back barricade .
That 's what we 're doing here .
I want you both to stay in this car , do you understand me ?
I don 't want you to move . You 'll be safe .
- It 's almost over . - Don 't , please .
Let go of my arm .
You can just stay here with us .
- And we can drive away and it 'll be fine . - Let go of my arm .
Let go of my arm .
No , please . I know . I 'm so sorry .
I 'm so sorry about what happened to your son .
Let go of my arm !
Stay in this car .
( RAPID TICKING )
WOMAN : ( ON TV ) There are five minutes remaining in this year 's Purge .
Hey .
- ( MAN GRUNTS ) - ( WOMAN GASPS )
No ! Don 't talk .
Shut your mouth . I 'm not here for your kids .
- I 'm here for you . - MAN : Okay .
Get up .
MAN : No , no , no .
- Come on , come on , come on . Get up , get up , get up . - ( WOMAN GRUNTING )
MAN : No , please don 't ...
Shut up , or I 'll shoot you in the face !
- Shut up ! Get down ! - MAN : Okay ! Okay , okay !
You get on your stomach . Lay down , flat .
- Look at me . Look at me . - MAN : Okay , okay .
- Look at my face . - Okay .
- Do you remember me ? Look at my face ! - Okay .
- Do you know what you took from me ? - I know .
You took my boy ! You took my boy ! You took my fucking boy !
- MAN : I am so sorry . - You took my son .
You killed my son , you son of a bitch !
WOMAN : Please ! Please don 't do this .
Look at me . Look at my face .
Did you see him when you hit him ? Did you see him ?
Tell me what he looks like . Tell me what he looked like !
- Tell me what he looks like . - MAN : I 'm so sorry for what I did .
Tell me you saw his face !
- Tell me you saw his face ! - I saw him .
You 're gonna pay for what you did to me .
- For what you did to my boy . - No , please .
MAN : Please !
( SCREAMING )
( GUNSHOTS )
( PANTING )
( GROANING )
We found your car , Sergeant .
Your plates told us who you were .
It was easy to see where you were headed tonight .
Hell , I would 've done the same thing .
There 's an unwritten Purge rule , Sergeant .
Don 't save lives .
Tonight , we take lives .
We make things manageable for us .
Unfortunately , the citizens aren 't killing enough .
So , we supplement it all to keep things balanced .
It 's important work the NFFA does ,
and we can 't have any interference .
We can 't have heroes .
Oh , no , sir .
No heroes .
I hope you feel cleansed .
Blessed be America ,
( COCKING GUN )
a nation reborn .
( GUNSHOT )
( INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO )
( ALARM RINGING )
Oh , no . Oh , God .
EVA : Oh , my God .
Oh .
( PANTING ) You got a car ?
- Uh ... Uh , yes . - You got a fucking car ?
- Go get it now ! - Yes , okay . Okay !
EVA : Okay !
Okay . Come on , Cali .
Come here and help me now , okay ?
Look at me ! Do you want him to survive ?
Then it 's up to us . We gotta help him now , okay ? Okay ?
On three , we 're gonna pick him up .
One , two , three !
- ( SERGEANT GRUNTING ) - Come on !
Come on !
Hurry up and get that car !
Okay .
- Hospital 's not far . We 'll be there in minutes . - ( SERGEANT GROANING )
Come on , just hit it ! Go , go , go !
( PANTING )
You did it .
You saved us .
So , please , just let us take care of you , okay ?
( SIRENS WAILING )
( HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING )
It 's over . It 's over .
MAN : ( OVER SPEAKER ) Just after 7 : 00 a.m. , March 22nd ,
and The Annual Purge has just concluded .
This is your American morning news program .
Reports are coming in from all around the country ,
as police , firefighters and paramedics take to the streets ,
assisting victims of last night .